<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <description></description>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 23:11:20 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 23:11:20 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Post</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Great things are just begining! Here at Spurred Studio we are doing everything we can to push out our first bit of content. Keep in mind that just because the content is being pushed out does not mean it is finished by any means. We hope to use this webspace as a way to push content out easily for testing. Once the content is finished players will be able to find it on more mainstream platforms like IOS, android, and facebook.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to follow along as we polish our games feel free to like follow and subscribe to our social media accounts. We will do our best to keep everyone updated when interesting things happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shortly after this website is deployed we will publish our first bit of content in the form of a Discord Bot. Discord is an amazing VoiP program for gamers, or anyone that uses a computer and needs to talk to others. We wanted to make our bot public so that others looking to make their own bot could learn what to do, or at least what not to do. We will dedicate a post to its release as well.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>/blog/first-post</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/blog/first-post</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Discord Bot</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Discord Bot is a visual studio solution made out of almost entirely C#. Though the Discord Bot was used as a learning tool so not everything is as well programmed as it could be. That being said the Discord Bot is programmed with the idea of private use in mind and not for use on multiple servers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is a list of the features available in the Discord Bot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Music - Users can request songs right off youtube&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Imgur - get random photos from imgur subreddits&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Vote Ban - can vote to ban non Mod players&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Clean Chat - Mods can delete messages from chat&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fun Commands - Commands like 8ball, roll, and raffle&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Admin Only Commands - Commands used to manage server&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Clean Chat - Mods can delete messages from chat&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grant Channel - Mods can grant other users channels&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Admin Text Channel - Shows who was using what admin command&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Twitter Feeds - Post recent tweets from a given twitter account every 60 seconds. At the moment to change twitter feeds you have to edit the code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though The bot is tailored to our Discord server so it will not work right out of the box. However once you have replaced a few lines of code to tailor the bot to your server it should run just fine. Specifically login information for the bot and twitter feed would need to be changed, and a couple lines that store channel and role information.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>/blog/discord-bot</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/blog/discord-bot</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
